<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Biscuits in Tea...!</title>
    <link>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Biscuits in Tea...!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 21:43:18 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://raghuugare.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World! :-) </title>
      <link>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Nov 2018 21:43:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/hello/</guid>
      <description> Hello, World! Well, let us begin with a customary program that simply prints a welcome message!
A simple program in C:
 An equivalent program in C++ is below:
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Genius of Ramanujan</title>
      <link>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/genius_of_ramanujan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/genius_of_ramanujan/</guid>
      <description>A glimpse of the great Indian mathe-magician’s work&amp;hellip; History has seldom seen a person who was so passionate, unorthodox, as well as gifted in a field, as was Srinivasa Ramanujan, the self-taught Indian genius, who made several startling discoveries in the realm of Mathematics.
Despite abject poverty and lack of formal training and encouragement, Ramanujan’s love for numbers never waned. And thanks to a chance encounter and ensuing collaboration with G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LISP : consp or listp ?</title>
      <link>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/subtle_difference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 17:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/subtle_difference/</guid>
      <description>I recently began my long-awaited journey(or a pilgrimage to be honest!) towards the wonderful &amp;lsquo;land&amp;rsquo; of LISP. And along the path, I started understanding the so-called predicates.1
I also began to learn about the predicates that are built-in, such as oddp, evenp, atomp, etc.
Then, I stumbled across what seemed like 2 different predicates that are &amp;lsquo;equivalent&amp;rsquo;, but which I realized are not exactly so.
So, I want to discuss briefly about the subtle difference between these 2 predicates viz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ode to LISP &lt;3 ! </title>
      <link>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/ode_to_lisp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/ode_to_lisp/</guid>
      <description>Finally, after a long time, I started my journey into the magical world of LISP&amp;ndash; something I&amp;rsquo;ve pined for long.
And began learning so many new things that I felt I should record my discoveries somewhere, more like a &amp;lsquo;travelogue&amp;rsquo; (or a monologue? :)).
Perhaps, someone travelling or planning to take this path will find it useful in someway, someday&amp;hellip;?
Prerequisites First, I made sure I had the following things sorted out:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Font-ification! :heart:</title>
      <link>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/fontification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2014 20:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://raghuugare.github.io/post/fontification/</guid>
      <description>My journey to the &amp;ldquo;font&amp;rdquo;ain of Beauty! :) I love fonts to an almost fanatic extent.
Other than meddling with different typefaces, with Serifs &amp;amp; without (&amp;lsquo;sans&amp;rsquo; 1 Serif), I have been notorious among my friends &amp;amp; peers for my heavy use of colors also to the above mix, giving rise to a &amp;lsquo;psychedelic riot of colors&amp;rsquo; in my blog articles &amp;amp; mails.
I do all of this&amp;mdash;in my effort to somehow produce &amp;lsquo;intonations &amp;amp; emphasis&amp;rsquo; of speech in written text, using colors, fonts and their weights &amp;amp; styles as my tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>